The Sikong family's realm
Государство рода Сыкун
Cannot be stained with the blood of our own clan again
не может больше проливать кровь родных
Father clearly said this wound was almost healed
Отец ясно говорил что рана почти зажила
How is this
почему же
I've thought for a long time
Папа долго думал
And decided to pass the throne to your elder brother
всё же решил передать трон твоему старшему брату
In times of chaos
В эпоху смут
Xuan Kingdom needs bravery
государству Сюань нужны отважные
Fierceness and ruthlessness
беспощадные люди готовые на всё
But to govern in peace
Но для управления мирным временем
Your elder brother is more suitable than I
твой брат подходит лучше
Or you
и меня и тебя
More suitable
гораздо лучше
Do you think I'm being unfair?
Думаешь отец поступает несправедливо
No
Нет
Your son is willing to assist elder brother
Я готов помогать старшему брату
I remember everything
Папа всё помнит
The Tiannan Pass battlefield
На поле боя у заставы Тяньнань
You alone lured Shilang into the pass
ты один заманил Шилана в проход
That battle
В том бою
You were hit by two blades
тебя ранили два раза
Got back on your horse and fought again
но ты продолжал сражаться верхом
Further north
А на севере
Your chest
на твоей груди
Shoulder
плече
Back
спине
All have arrow wounds
всё в ранах от стрел
Every wound you suffered for Xuan Kingdom
Каждую рану что ты получил за Сюань
I remember
папа помнит
Father
Папа
Your temper is most like mine
У тебя характер как у меня
I sometimes think
Папа думал
When the realm is at peace
когда наступит мир
You can travel the mountains and rivers for me
ты поедешь вместо меня странствовать по горам и рекам
See beautiful scenery and people everywhere
любоваться красотами и женщинами
Free as an immortal
жить как божество
But after all, some things
Но всё же есть дела
I must burden you with
которые папа вынужден возложить на тебя
Father
Папа
Your elder brother has it hard
Твоему брату будет непросто
Help him for me
Поддержи его вместо меня
Assist him
помогай ему
And protect what we two
И храни те земли
Worked so hard to conquer
которые мы с тобой с таким трудом завоевали
Second son
Младший сын
Can you promise me?
ты обещаешь папе
Your son promises
Я обещаю папе
Your son guarantees to do everything to protect Xuan Kingdom
Клянусь отцу я приложу все силы чтобы сохранить государство Сюань
Rise
Встань
Good child
Хорошо